Usage: C:\cmdstan\examples\bernoulli\bernoulli.exe <arg1> <subarg1_1> ... <subarg1_m> ... <arg_n> <subarg_n_1> ... <subarg_n_m>

Begin by selecting amongst the following inference methods and diagnostics,
  sample      Bayesian inference with Markov Chain Monte Carlo
  optimize    Point estimation
  variational  Variational inference
  diagnose    Model diagnostics
  generate_quantities  Generate quantities of interest
  pathfinder  Pathfinder algorithm
  log_prob    Return the log density up to a constant and its gradients, given supplied parameters
  laplace     Sample from a Laplace approximation

Or see help information with
  help        Prints help
  help-all    Prints entire argument tree

Additional configuration available by specifying
  id          Unique process identifier
  data        Input data options
  init        Initialization method: "x" initializes randomly between [-x, x], "0" initializes to 0, anything else identifies a file of values. If multiple chains are run, this can either be a single path, in which case its name will have _ID appended, or a comma-separated list of names.
  random      Random number configuration
  output      File output options
  num_threads  Number of threads available to the program. To use this argument, re-compile this model with STAN_THREADS=true.

See C:\cmdstan\examples\bernoulli\bernoulli.exe <arg1> [ help | help-all ] for details on individual arguments.

